[{"answer": "Hi Robert.  How are you", "docId": "02-07", "aSentId": 12, "question": "", "qSentId": 11},{"answer": " Hey, Doreen.  Im doing pretty well.  How about you", "docId": "02-07", "aSentId": 13, "question": "Hi Robert.  How are you", "qSentId": 12},{"answer": " Im good too, thank you.  I was just stopping by to see how you were doing a", "docId": "02-07", "aSentId": 14, "question": " Hey, Doreen.  Im doing pretty well.  How about you", "qSentId": 13},{"answer": " Its going well.  Im still learning the ropes, but everything has been going fine", "docId": "02-07", "aSentId": 18, "question": " Im good too, thank you.  I was just stopping by to see how you were doing a", "qSentId": 17},{"answer": " I can imagine.  Do you like your new office", "docId": "02-07", "aSentId": 22, "question": " Its going well.  Im still learning the ropes, but everything has been going fine", "qSentId": 21},{"answer": " Oh, yeah.  Its great to have so much room", "docId": "02-07", "aSentId": 23, "question": " I can imagine.  Do you like your new office", "qSentId": 22},{"answer": " Im glad to hear that.  Do you need any equipment or supplies?  Im putting a", "docId": "02-07", "aSentId": 24, "question": " Oh, yeah.  Its great to have so much room", "qSentId": 23},{"answer": " Actually, there are a few things Ive been thinking about", "docId": "02-07", "aSentId": 28, "question": " Im glad to hear that.  Do you need any equipment or supplies?  Im putting a", "qSentId": 27},{"answer": " OK.  What do you need", "docId": "02-07", "aSentId": 29, "question": " Actually, there are a few things Ive been thinking about", "qSentId": 28},{"answer": " Well, my computer hasnt been running too well.  The monitor seems prett", "docId": "02-07", "aSentId": 33, "question": " OK.  What do you need", "qSentId": 32},{"answer": " Yeah.  I think you have the oldest computer in the office.  It gets passed dow", "docId": "02-07", "aSentId": 37, "question": " Well, my computer hasnt been running too well.  The monitor seems prett", "qSentId": 36},{"answer": " Well, could I get an ergonomic keyboard?  I can type a lot faster with one o", "docId": "02-07", "aSentId": 41, "question": " Yeah.  I think you have the oldest computer in the office.  It gets passed dow", "qSentId": 40},{"answer": " Id just like one that rises up and down and has arms", "docId": "02-07", "aSentId": 47, "question": " Well, could I get an ergonomic keyboard?  I can type a lot faster with one o", "qSentId": 46},{"answer": " Sure.  We can order that", "docId": "02-07", "aSentId": 52, "question": " Id just like one that rises up and down and has arms", "qSentId": 51},{"answer": " I was wondering about something else too", "docId": "02-07", "aSentId": 53, "question": " Sure.  We can order that", "qSentId": 52},{"answer": " Whats that", "docId": "02-07", "aSentId": 54, "question": " I was wondering about something else too", "qSentId": 53},{"answer": " Well, I do a lot of communication with our overseas clients.  Is it possible to ge", "docId": "02-07", "aSentId": 55, "question": " Whats that", "qSentId": 54},{"answer": " Yes.  You know, weve been thinking about getting this kind of equipment fo", "docId": "02-07", "aSentId": 59, "question": " Well, I do a lot of communication with our overseas clients.  Is it possible to ge", "qSentId": 58},{"answer": " I think thats a great idea.  Its so much easier and cheaper to do things tha", "docId": "02-07", "aSentId": 64, "question": " Yes.  You know, weve been thinking about getting this kind of equipment fo", "qSentId": 63},{"answer": " The boss likes to hear that kind of thinking!  Let me talk with him abou", "docId": "02-07", "aSentId": 66, "question": " I think thats a great idea.  Its so much easier and cheaper to do things tha", "qSentId": 65},{"answer": " Sounds great", "docId": "02-07", "aSentId": 71, "question": " The boss likes to hear that kind of thinking!  Let me talk with him abou", "qSentId": 70},{"answer": " Anything else", "docId": "02-07", "aSentId": 72, "question": " Sounds great", "qSentId": 71},{"answer": " There was one more thing.  I hope Im not asking too much, but can I get a ne", "docId": "02-07", "aSentId": 73, "question": " Anything else", "qSentId": 72},{"answer": " I think thats an old chair too.  Sorry about that.  Is there a specific kind yo", "docId": "02-07", "aSentId": 77, "question": " There was one more thing.  I hope Im not asking too much, but can I get a ne", "qSentId": 76},{"answer": " No problem.  You do sit a lot, so well try to get you a good, comfortable one.  ", "docId": "02-07", "aSentId": 80, "question": " I think thats an old chair too.  Sorry about that.  Is there a specific kind yo", "qSentId": 79},{"answer": " Sure.  Thats fine", "docId": "02-07", "aSentId": 84, "question": " No problem.  You do sit a lot, so well try to get you a good, comfortable one.  ", "qSentId": 83},{"answer": " Anything else", "docId": "02-07", "aSentId": 85, "question": " Sure.  Thats fine", "qSentId": 84},{"answer": " No, I think thats it.  Sorry to ask for so much", "docId": "02-07", "aSentId": 86, "question": " Anything else", "qSentId": 85},{"answer": " No, its OK.  We want to make sure you have all the right equipment to perfor", "docId": "02-07", "aSentId": 87, "question": " No, I think thats it.  Sorry to ask for so much", "qSentId": 86},{"answer": " Thank you!  I really appreciate that", "docId": "02-07", "aSentId": 90, "question": " No, its OK.  We want to make sure you have all the right equipment to perfor", "qSentId": 89},{"answer": " Youre welcome.  So, Ill get back to you about the headset and web cam an", "docId": "02-07", "aSentId": 91, "question": " Thank you!  I really appreciate that", "qSentId": 90},{"answer": " OK.  I will.  Thank, Doreen", "docId": "02-07", "aSentId": 95, "question": " Youre welcome.  So, Ill get back to you about the headset and web cam an", "qSentId": 94},{"answer": " See you later", "docId": "02-07", "aSentId": 96, "question": " OK.  I will.  Thank, Doreen", "qSentId": 95}]
